# Paulo Junior | .NET Developer

<u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>□+55 21976650546</u> | <u>Mpf.junior89@gmail.com</u> | <u>GitHub</u>

#### About me

I've been working as software developer for over five years, with expertise in backend development, working with the Microsoft technology, such as C# and .NET, always striving for code that follow good software practices and principles. Also, I have some knowledge of front-end technology, such as ASP.NET MVC and Angular.

#### Skills

- C# | .NET | .NET Framework | ASP.NET MVC | ASP.NET WebAPI | ASP.NET Blazor | EF Core | SQL Server | MySQL | PostgreSQL
- SOLID | DDD | Clean Architecture | RabbitMQ
- Angular | TypeScript | Boostrap | Git | Docker | Azure DevOps | Portuguese Native | English B1

# Experience

### Software Developer

Ilha Service

On Site. Brazil

06/2024 - Current

Outsourced to a public agency, responsible for sustaining the systems for internal and external use.

#### Developer Analyst

Stefanini

Remote, Brazil 09/2022 - 04/2023

- I participated in the development of a web api that would be consumed by a game that was developed for the metaverse. This web api would receive some game data for persistence in the database. The web api was developed in dotnet core, version 6. With EF Core and SQLite database. The publication was using containers.
- Development and support of software for a fast-food client.

#### Back-End Developer

Conexa Aliare

Remote, Brazil 07/2022 - 09/2022

• Develop new features and support for an agricultural defensive recipe software.

.NET Developer

Meta

Remote. Brazil 05/2021 - 06/2022

- Software for the company of the import and export segment: Develop new features (frontend / backend); Code support.
- Benefits segment software: Screen automation testing.

## Full-Stack Developer

Hera Informatica

Remote, Brazil

05/2019 - 05/2021

- Migration of the natural gas management system from .NET Framework 4.x to .NET Core and Angular.
- Migration of the mobile app from java/android to Flutter.
- Web system and app mobile support.

System Analyst

Rightway

On Site. Brazil 10/2018 - 12/2018

• Development and support a web system.

System Analyst

**Hera Informatica** 

On Site, Brazil 07/2016 - 02/2017

Responsible for sustaining the management system of the natural gas sector.

#### **Education**

Specialization in .NET Software Engineering

Instituto Infnet

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil 02/2018 - 12/2022

Bachelor's Degree in Information Systems

**FEUC** 

Rio de Janeiro,

Brazil

08/2007 - 12/2011

# **Licenses & certifications**

- Foundational C# with Microsoft Free Code Camp (02/2024)
- AZ-900: Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamentals Microsoft (06/2022)